hornby.com 2017-05-30

# Hornby Privacy Policy

**Introduction- Our commitment to privacy**

Hornby America respects each individual’s right to personal privacy. We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described below without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Part I. Information Collection**

Hornby America collects information through our Web site at several points. We collect the following information about primary visitors such as name and address information.

We may also collect contact information that our users divulge about other people, for the use of referrals. Hornby America does not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child under 13 to divulge personal information.

We collect the following general data that is not personally identifiable information pertaining to site traffic. We collect this information through click stream tracking and automatic logging files. This general information is collected automatically and is not connected to specific user data. 

We may employ the use of cookies. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user’s computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable Hornby America to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users. Our cookies usually have an expiration date. Our cookies do not collect personally identifiable information.

**Part II. Information Usage**

The information collected by Hornby America will be used for internal use. Users who provide information may receive email announcements or updates concerning our products or services.

Registered users may receive additional announcements from us about products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications by contacting us directly.

The information we collect will not be used to create customer profiles based on browsing or purchasing history. We will not supplement information collected at our Web site with data from other sources such as credit history to authorize purchases.

We will share data with our transaction gateway only for the purposes of authorizing your purchase. We may have links to other sites from ours. Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Their standards may differ from ours.

**Part III. Data Storage and Security**

Hornby America protects user information using secure servers, firewalls and SSL encryption to protect consumer privacy. General order information such as contact data is saved securely in our database. For your privacy and protection only the last four digits of your credit card and your expiration date are stored in our servers.  Your credit card number is only securely passed on to the transaction gateway to process your order.

**Part IV. Changes in this Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

**Part V. Problem Resolution**

We are committed to resolving disputes within a timely matter. If problems arise, users may contact us at:

Hornby America  
3900-C2 Industry Dr. East  
Fife, WA. 98424  
Telephone: 877-358-6405  
Fax: 253-922-7203  
Email: [customersupport@hornby.us ](http://hornby.ditest.us/pages/customersupport@hornby.us%20)
